<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Programmer\'s toolbox</string>
    <string name="title_note_activity">Note</string>
    <string name="action_make_note">Make a note</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_text">Let\'s learn something!</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close drawer</string>
    <string name="note_hint">Write your note</string>
    <string name="technology_icon_content_description">Technology logo</string>

    <string-array name="categories">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>JS SPA Frameworks</item>
        <item>Java Web Frameworks</item>
        <item>PHP Frameworks</item>
        <item>Python Web Frameworks</item>
        <item>CSS Frameworks</item>
        <item>Java Application Servers</item>
        <item>Database Management Softwares</item>
        <item>Version Control Systems</item>
        <item>Linux Distributions</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="js_spa_frameworks">
        <item>AngularJS</item>
        <item>Ember.js</item>
        <item>ExtJS</item>
        <item>Knockout.js</item>
        <item>Meteor.js</item>
        <item>Aurelia</item>
        <item>Vue.js</item>
        <item>React</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="java_web_frameworks">
        <item>JSF</item>
        <item>Struts</item>
        <item>Hibernate</item>
        <item>GWT</item>
        <item>Vaadin</item>
        <item>Wicket</item>
        <item>Vert.X</item>
        <item>Spring MVC</item>
        <item>Play!</item>
        <item>Grails</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="php_frameworks">
        <item>Laravel</item>
        <item>Symfony</item>
        <item>CodeIgniter</item>
        <item>Yii 2</item>
        <item>Phalcon</item>
        <item>CakePHP</item>
        <item>Zend Framework</item>
        <item>Slim</item>
        <item>FuelPHP</item>
        <item>PHPixie</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="to_add">
        <item>Technology has not been added yet</item>
        <item>Technology has not been added yet</item>
        <item>Technology has not been added yet</item>
        <item>Technology has not been added yet</item>
        <item>Technology has not been added yet</item>
        <item>Technology has not been added yet</item>
        <item>Technology has not been added yet</item>
        <item>Technology has not been added yet</item>
        <item>Technology has not been added yet</item>
        <item>Technology has not been added yet</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="java_web_frameworks_descriptions">
        <item>JavaServer Faces (JSF) is a Java specification for building component-based user
            interfaces for web applications and was formalized as a standard through the Java
            Community Process being part of the Java Platform, Enterprise Edition.
            It is also a MVC web framework that simplifies construction of user interfaces (UI)
            for server-based applications by using reusable UI components in a page.</item>
        <item>Apache Struts is an open-source web application framework for developing Java EE web
            applications. It uses and extends the Java Servlet API to encourage developers to adopt
            a model–view–controller (MVC) architecture. It was originally created by Craig McClanahan
            and donated to the Apache Foundation in May 2000. Formerly located under the Apache Jakarta
            Project and known as Jakarta Struts, it became a top-level Apache project in 2005.</item>
        <item>Hibernate ORM (Hibernate in short) is an object-relational mapping tool for the
            Java programming language. It provides a framework for mapping an object-oriented
            domain model to a relational database. Hibernate handles object-relational impedance
            mismatch problems by replacing direct, persistent database accesses with high-level
            object handling functions. Hibernate\'s primary feature is mapping from Java classes
            to database tables, and mapping from Java data types to SQL data types. Hibernate also
            provides data query and retrieval facilities. It generates SQL calls and relieves the
            developer from the manual handling and object conversion of the result set.</item>
        <item>Google Web Toolkit (GWT), or GWT Web Toolkit, is an open source set of tools
            that allows web developers to create and maintain complex JavaScript front-end
            applications in Java. Other than a few native libraries, everything is Java source
            that can be built on any supported platform with the included GWT Ant build files.
            It is licensed under the Apache License version 2.0. GWT emphasizes reusable approaches
            to common web development tasks, namely asynchronous remote procedure calls, history
            management, bookmarking, UI abstraction, internationalization, and cross-browser portability.</item>
        <item>Vaadin is an open-source platform for web application development. The Vaadin platform
            includes a set of web components, a Java web framework, and a set of tools and application
            starters. It\'s flagship product, Vaadin Flow (previously Vaadin Framework) allows the
            implementation of HTML5 web user interfaces using the Java Programming Language.</item>
        <item>Apache Wicket, commonly referred to as Wicket, is a lightweight component-based web
            application framework for the Java programming language conceptually similar to JavaServer
            Faces and Tapestry. It was originally written by Jonathan Locke in April 2004. Version
            1.0 was released in June 2005. It graduated into an Apache top-level project in June 2007.</item>
        <item>Vert.x is incredibly flexible - whether it\'s simple network utilities, sophisticated
            modern web applications, HTTP/REST microservices, high volume event processing or a full
            blown back-end message-bus application, Vert.x is a great fit. Vert.x is used by many
            different companies from real-time gaming to banking and everything in between.</item>
        <item>The Spring Framework is an application framework and inversion of control container
            for the Java platform. The framework\'s core features can be used by any Java application,
            but there are extensions for building web applications on top of the Java EE (Enterprise Edition)
            platform. Although the framework does not impose any specific programming model, it has
            become popular in the Java community as an addition to, or even replacement for the Enterprise
            JavaBeans (EJB) model. The Spring Framework is open source.</item>
        <item>Play Framework is an open-source web application framework, written in Scala and also usable
            from other programming languages that are compiled to Bytecode, e.g. Java, which follows the
            model–view–controller (MVC) architectural pattern. It aims to optimize developer productivity by
            using convention over configuration, hot code reloading and display of errors in the browser.
            Support for the Scala programming language has been available since version 1.1 of the framework.
            In version 2.0, the framework core was rewritten in Scala. Build and deployment was migrated to SBT,
            and templates use Scala instead of Apache Groovy.</item>
        <item>Grails is an open source web application framework that uses the Apache Groovy programming language
            (which is in turn based on the Java platform). It is intended to be a high-productivity framework by
            following the "coding by convention" paradigm, providing a stand-alone development environment and
            hiding much of the configuration detail from the developer.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="js.spa_frameworks_descriptions">
        <item>AngularJS is a JavaScript-based open-source front-end web application framework mainly maintained
            by Google and by a community of individuals and corporations to address many of the challenges encountered
            in developing single-page applications. The JavaScript components complement Apache Cordova, a framework
            used for developing cross-platform mobile apps. It aims to simplify both the development and the testing
            of such applications by providing a framework for client-side model–view–controller (MVC) and model–view–viewmodel
            (MVVM) architectures, along with components commonly used in rich Internet applications.</item>
        <item>Ember.js is an open-source JavaScript web framework, based on the Model–view–viewmodel (MVVM) pattern. It
            allows developers to create scalable single-page web applications by incorporating common idioms and best
            practices into the framework. Ember is used on many popular websites, including Discourse, Groupon, LinkedIn,
            Vine, Live Nation, Nordstrom, Twitch.tv and Chipotle. Although primarily considered a framework for the web,
            it is also possible to build desktop and mobile applications in Ember. The most notable example of an Ember
            desktop application is Apple Music, a feature of the iTunes desktop application.</item>
        <item>Ext JS is a pure JavaScript application framework for building interactive cross platform web applications
            using techniques such as Ajax, DHTML and DOM scripting. It can be used as a simple component framework
            (to e.g. create dynamic grids on otherwise static pages), but also as a full framework for building single-page
            applications. Originally built as an add-on library extension of YUI by Jack Slocum on April 15, 2007, beginning
            with version 1.1, Ext JS retains no dependencies on external libraries, instead making their use optional.</item>
        <item>Knockout is a standalone JavaScript implementation of the Model-View-ViewModel pattern with templates. The
            underlying principles are a clear separation between domain data, view components and data to be displayed and
            the presence of a clearly defined layer of specialized code to manage the relationships between the view components.
            The latter leverages the native event management features of the JavaScript language. These features streamline and
            simplify the specification of complex relationships between view components, which in turn make the display more
            responsive and the user experience richer.</item>
        <item>Meteor, or MeteorJS, is a free and open-source isomorphic JavaScript web framework written using Node.js. Meteor
            allows for rapid prototyping and produces cross-platform (Android, iOS, Web) code. It integrates with MongoDB and
            uses the Distributed Data Protocol and a publish–subscribe pattern to automatically propagate data changes to clients
            without requiring the developer to write any synchronization code. On the client, Meteor can be used with its own
            Blaze templating engine, as well as with the Angular or React frameworks.</item>
        <item>Aurelia is a collection of Modern JavaScript modules, which when used together, function as a powerful platform
            for building browser, desktop and mobile applications, all open source and built on open web standards. Rather than
            being a monolithic framework, Aurelia is broken down into a collection of feature-oriented modules. Examples of
            feature modules include metadata, dependency injection, binding, templating, router and more. Each module is written
            using ECMAScript (aka JavaScript) or TypeScript (a strict superset of JavaScript that adds compile-time type checking).
            Many of these modules can be used individually in any type of JavaScript project, including Node.js.</item>
        <item>Vue.js is an open-source JavaScript framework for building user interfaces. Integration into projects that use
            other JavaScript libraries is simplified with Vue because it is designed to be incrementally adoptable. Vue can also
            function as a web application framework capable of powering advanced single-page applications. The project focuses
            on making ideas in web UI development (components, declarative UI, hot-reloading, time-travel debugging, etc.) more
            approachable. It attempts to be less opinionated and thus easier for developers to pick up. It features an incrementally
            adoptable architecture.</item>
        <item>In computing, React (also known as React.js or ReactJS) is a JavaScript library for building user interfaces. It is
            maintained by Facebook and a community of individual developers and companies. React can be used as a base in the development
            of single-page or mobile applications. Complex React applications usually require the use of additional libraries for
            state management, routing, and interaction with an API.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="php_frameworks_descriptions">
        <item>Laravel is a free, open-source PHP web framework, created by Taylor Otwell and intended for the development of web
            applications following the model–view–controller (MVC) architectural pattern and based on Symfony. Some of the features
            of Laravel are a modular packaging system with a dedicated dependency manager, different ways for accessing relational
            databases, utilities that aid in application deployment and maintenance, and its orientation toward syntactic sugar.</item>
        <item>Symfony is a PHP web application framework and a set of reusable PHP components/libraries created to speed up the
            creation and maintenance of web applications and to replace repetitive coding tasks. Symfony has a low performance
            overhead used with a bytecode cache.</item>
        <item>CodeIgniter is an open-source software rapid development web framework, for use in building dynamic web sites with
            PHP. It is loosely based on the popular model–view–controller (MVC) development pattern. While controller classes are
            a necessary part of development under CodeIgniter, models and views are optional. Codeigniter can be also modified to
            use Hierarchical Model View Controller (HMVC) which allows developers to maintain modular grouping of Controller,
            Models and View arranged in a sub-directory format.</item>
        <item>Yii 2 is purely object-oriented, and it\’s based on the DRY (Don’t Repeat Yourself) coding concept, so it provides
            you with a pretty clean and logical code base. Yii 2 is integrated with jQuery, and it comes with a set of AJAX-enabled
            features, and it implements an easy-to-use skinning and theming mechanism, so it can be a great choice for someone who
            comes from a frontend background.</item>
        <item>Phalcon is a PHP web framework based on the model–view–controller (MVC) pattern. Unlike most PHP frameworks, Phalcon
            is implemented as a web server extension written in Zephir and C, aiming to boost execution speed, reduce resource usage,
            and handle more HTTP requests per second than comparable frameworks written primarily in PHP. One drawback of this
            approach is that root/administrative access is required on the server to install Phalcon by building a custom binary or
            using a precompiled one.</item>
        <item>CakePHP is an open-source web framework. It follows the model–view–controller (MVC) approach and is written in PHP,
            modeled after the concepts of Ruby on Rails, and distributed under the MIT License. CakePHP uses well-known software
            engineering concepts and software design patterns, such as convention over configuration, model–view–controller, active
            record, association data mapping, and front controller.</item>
        <item>Zend Framework is an open source, object-oriented web application framework implemented in PHP 7 and licensed under the
            New BSD License. The framework is basically a collection of professional PHP based packages. The framework uses various
            packages by the use of Composer as part of its package dependency managers; some of them are PHP unit for testing all
            packages, Travis CI for continuous Integration Services. Zend Framework provides to users a support of the Model View
            Controller (MVC) in combination with Front Controller solution.</item>
        <item>Slim is a PHP micro framework that provides you with everything you need and nothing you don\’t. Micro frameworks are
            minimalistic in design, they are excellent for smaller apps where a full-stack framework would be an exaggeration. Slim\’s
            creator was inspired by a Ruby micro framework called Sinatra. Slim is used by many PHP developers for developing RESTful
            APIs and services. Slim comes with features such as URL routing, client-side HTTP caching, session- and cookie encryption,
            and it supports “flash” messages across HTTP requests as well.</item>
        <item>FuelPHP is a flexible full-stack PHP framework that doesn\’t only support the ordinary MVC pattern but also its evolved
            version, HMVC (Hierarchical Model-View-Controller) at the architecture level. FuelPHP adds an optional class called
            Presenter (formerly called ViewModel) between the Controller and View layers to hold the logic needed to generate Views.
            FuelPHP is modular and extendable, takes care of security concerns by providing features such as input and URI filtering
            and output encoding, and it comes with its own authentication framework, with many other sophisticated features and a
            detailed documentation.</item>
        <item>PHPixie is a quite new framework, it started in 2012 with the goal of creating a high-performance framework for read-only
            websites. PHPixie also implements the HMVC design pattern just like FuelPHP, and is built by using independent components
            that can be used as well without the framework itself. The PHPixie components are 100% unit tested, and require minimum
            dependencies.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="to_add_descriptions">
        <item>Description for this technology has not been added yet.</item>
        <item>Description for this technology has not been added yet.</item>
        <item>Description for this technology has not been added yet.</item>
        <item>Description for this technology has not been added yet.</item>
        <item>Description for this technology has not been added yet.</item>
        <item>Description for this technology has not been added yet.</item>
        <item>Description for this technology has not been added yet.</item>
        <item>Description for this technology has not been added yet.</item>
        <item>Description for this technology has not been added yet.</item>
        <item>Description for this technology has not been added yet.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
