<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Programmer\'s toolbox</string>
    <string name="title_note_activity">Note</string>
    <string name="action_make_note">Make a note</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_text">Lets learn something!</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close drawer</string>
    <string name="note_hint">Write your note</string>
    <string-array name="categories">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>JS SPA frameworks</item>
        <item>Java Web frameworks</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="js_spa_frameworks">
        <item>AngularJS</item>
        <item>Ember.js</item>
        <item>ExtJS</item>
        <item>Knockout.js</item>
        <item>Meteor.js</item>
        <item>Aurelia</item>
        <item>Vue.js</item>
        <item>React</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="java_web_frameworks">
        <item>JSF</item>
        <item>Struts</item>
        <item>Hibernate</item>
        <item>GWT</item>
        <item>Vaadin</item>
        <item>Wicket</item>
        <item>Vert.X</item>
        <item>Spring MVC</item>
        <item>Play!</item>
        <item>Grails</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="java_web_frameworks_descriptions">
        <item>JavaServer Faces (JSF) is a Java specification for building component-based user
            interfaces for web applications and was formalized as a standard through the Java
            Community Process being part of the Java Platform, Enterprise Edition.
            It is also a MVC web framework that simplifies construction of user interfaces (UI)
            for server-based applications by using reusable UI components in a page.</item>
        <item>Apache Struts is an open-source web application framework for developing Java EE web
            applications. It uses and extends the Java Servlet API to encourage developers to adopt
            a model–view–controller (MVC) architecture. It was originally created by Craig McClanahan
            and donated to the Apache Foundation in May 2000. Formerly located under the Apache Jakarta
            Project and known as Jakarta Struts, it became a top-level Apache project in 2005.</item>
        <item>Hibernate ORM (Hibernate in short) is an object-relational mapping tool for the
            Java programming language. It provides a framework for mapping an object-oriented
            domain model to a relational database. Hibernate handles object-relational impedance
            mismatch problems by replacing direct, persistent database accesses with high-level
            object handling functions. Hibernate's primary feature is mapping from Java classes
            to database tables, and mapping from Java data types to SQL data types. Hibernate also
            provides data query and retrieval facilities. It generates SQL calls and relieves the
            developer from the manual handling and object conversion of the result set.</item>
        <item>Google Web Toolkit (GWT), or GWT Web Toolkit, is an open source set of tools
            that allows web developers to create and maintain complex JavaScript front-end
            applications in Java. Other than a few native libraries, everything is Java source
            that can be built on any supported platform with the included GWT Ant build files.
            It is licensed under the Apache License version 2.0. GWT emphasizes reusable approaches
            to common web development tasks, namely asynchronous remote procedure calls, history
            management, bookmarking, UI abstraction, internationalization, and cross-browser portability.</item>
        <item>Vaadin is an open-source platform for web application development. The Vaadin platform
            includes a set of web components, a Java web framework, and a set of tools and application
            starters. It's flagship product, Vaadin Flow (previously Vaadin Framework) allows the
            implementation of HTML5 web user interfaces using the Java Programming Language.</item>
        <item>Apache Wicket, commonly referred to as Wicket, is a lightweight component-based web
            application framework for the Java programming language conceptually similar to JavaServer
            Faces and Tapestry. It was originally written by Jonathan Locke in April 2004. Version
            1.0 was released in June 2005. It graduated into an Apache top-level project in June 2007.</item>
        <item>Vert.x is incredibly flexible - whether it's simple network utilities, sophisticated
            modern web applications, HTTP/REST microservices, high volume event processing or a full
            blown back-end message-bus application, Vert.x is a great fit. Vert.x is used by many
            different companies from real-time gaming to banking and everything in between.</item>
        <item>The Spring Framework is an application framework and inversion of control container
            for the Java platform. The framework's core features can be used by any Java application,
            but there are extensions for building web applications on top of the Java EE (Enterprise Edition)
            platform. Although the framework does not impose any specific programming model, it has
            become popular in the Java community as an addition to, or even replacement for the Enterprise
            JavaBeans (EJB) model. The Spring Framework is open source.</item>
        <item>Play Framework is an open-source web application framework, written in Scala and also usable
            from other programming languages that are compiled to Bytecode, e.g. Java, which follows the
            model–view–controller (MVC) architectural pattern. It aims to optimize developer productivity by
            using convention over configuration, hot code reloading and display of errors in the browser.
            Support for the Scala programming language has been available since version 1.1 of the framework.
            In version 2.0, the framework core was rewritten in Scala. Build and deployment was migrated to SBT,
            and templates use Scala instead of Apache Groovy.</item>
        <item>Grails is an open source web application framework that uses the Apache Groovy programming language
            (which is in turn based on the Java platform). It is intended to be a high-productivity framework by
            following the "coding by convention" paradigm, providing a stand-alone development environment and
            hiding much of the configuration detail from the developer.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
